A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, National Affairs Division, Vice President, Office Files of Mitchell Sviridoff FA577
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative Subject Files, 1966-1980; I; 13.67 Cubic Feet 13 letter document boxes
  - Juvenile and Children's Programs -- Correspondence and Background on Childhood Education (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Juvenile and Children's Programs -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Juvenile Delinquency (3 of 4), 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Juvenile and Children's Programs -- Correspondence, Proposals, Reports, Background (4 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Juvenile Justice -- Correspondence Re: Vera Institute Report, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - K-General -- Ted Kennedy, etc., 1971-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - K- Martin Luther King Jr. Center -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Grant Support, 1968-1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, Eamon -- Memoranda Re: Program Officers, Social Development, PRIs, etc., 1969-1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - L-General -- Levi-Strauss Foundation, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), etc. (1 of 2), 1971-1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - L-General -- Labor History, St. Louis Desegregation, etc. (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Looters Project, Jul 1977 -- Memoranda and Report on New York City Blackout Looting, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - M-General -- Minority Underrepresentation in Higher Education, Anita Miller on Urban Reinvestment, etc. (1 of 2), 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - M-General -- Nuclear Safety Manual After Three Mile Island, Migrant Workers, etc. (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mangum, Garth L. -- Correspondence on Ghettos, Legal Charges Against Mangum, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation -- Correspondence, Report on Supported Work (1 of 3), 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation -- Demonstration Project for Teenage Mothers (2 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation -- Supported Work, Congressional Hearings (3 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Maternity Leave Policy -- Memoranda Re: Ford Foundation Policy, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - May, Edgar -- Correspondence and Background on Drug Abuse and Treatment Programs, etc., 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miami-Dade County Riot -- White House Task Force Report, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Minority Economic Small Business Investment Corporations (MESBICs) -- Background on Ford Foundation Support, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Monitoring Reports of Ford Foundation Programs and Grantees (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Monitoring Reports of Ford Foundation Programs and Grantees (2 of 3), 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Monitoring Reports of Ford Foundation Programs and Grantees (3 of 3), 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mott Foundation -- Correspondence, Proposal for Educational and Service Enrichment for Youth Employment and Demonstration Project, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P. -- Correspondence Re: Urban Renewal, Background on Moynihan, 1973-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Ms. Foundation -- Correspondence with Gloria Steinem et al. Re: Ford Foundation Support, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - N-General -- New World Foundation, National Institute for Dispute Resolution, etc., 1975-1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Public Administration -- Memoranda, Background, Reevaluation of Proposal Status, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National Advisory Council of Minority Business Enterprise -- Minority Bank Deposits, etc., 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - National Affairs -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports on Ford Foundation, Organization Chart, 1968-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Affairs Budget -- Memoranda, Reports (1 of 2), 1971-1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Affairs Budget -- Memoranda, Reports (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - National Affairs Committee Meeting Re: Conflict Resolution, etc. -- Memoranda, Reports, Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - National Affairs Reports on National Affairs Programs (1 of 2), 1971-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - National Affairs Reports (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - National Affairs Retreat -- Reports, Memoranda Re: Grant Process and Evaluations, 1971 February (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development -- Correspondence, Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) -- Correspondence Re: Mississippi Civil Suit Appeal, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - National Center for Voluntary Action -- Proposal, Evaluation, Denial of Request, 1972 February-April (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - National Commission on Employment and Labor Statistics -- Discouraged Workers, Meetings, etc. (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - National Commission on Employment and Labor Statistics -- Federal Government Reports (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - National Urban Coalition -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Grant, 1972-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - National Urban League -- Correspondence, Proposal, Speeches and Writings by Vernon Jordan (1 of 2), 1968-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - National Urban League -- Correspondence, Speeches and Writings by Vernon Jordan (2 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - New Haven, CT -- Correspondence, Background on Urban Service Corps, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey Community Action Training Institute -- Correspondence, Training Manuals (1 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Community Action Training Institute -- Training Manuals for Anti-Poverty Community Action Workers (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - New York City Financial Crisis -- Implications for Ford Foundation -- Memoranda Re: Meetings, Background on Ford Foundation New York City Grants, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - New York City Financial Crisis -- New York Community Trust Multi-Foundation Meeting on City's Financial Crisis, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - New York City Financial Crisis -- Task Force on the New York City Crisis -- Correspondence, Working Documents, Minutes, Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina Fund -- Memoranda Re: Senate Investigation of Ford Foundation and NCF, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Nutrition -- Memoranda, Reports, Background for Ford Foundation Program Development (1 of 2), 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Nutrition -- Memoranda, Reports, Background for Ford Foundation Program Development (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - O-General -- Opportunity Funding Corporation, Office of Minority Business Enterprise, etc., 1969-1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Oakland Economic Development Council -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grants to City of Oakland, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Occupational Safety and Health -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Report on Workplace Health, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Office of Environmental Mediation, University of Washington -- Correspondence, Paper on Defining Environmental Mediation, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Oppenheimer-Nicolau, Siobhan -- Reports and Memoranda Re: Foundation Work with Hispanic Americans, 1969-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Oral History Project, Ford Foundation -- Correspondence and Agreement for Sviridoff's Interview, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Organized Crime Conference -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background on Ford Foundation Organized Crime Project (1 of 2), 1970-1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Organized Crime Conference -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background on Ford Foundation Organized Crime Project (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - P-General -- Private Industry Council, Puerto Rican Defense, Productivity, etc., 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - P- Committee on Public Policy -- Memoranda, Reports, Meetings, Grant Discussions (1 of 3), 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - P- Committee on Public Policy -- Meeting Minutes, Ford Foundation Program Review (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - P- Committee on Public Policy -- Meeting Minutes, Reports on Ethnic Tensions in Asia, Military Service and Society, etc. (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - P- Corporation for Public/Private Ventures -- Board Meetings, Reports on Corporation Activities, Background, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - P- School District of Philadelphia -- Correspondence Re: Proposal, Papers on Education by Graham S. Finney, 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - P- University of Pennsylvania Center for Urban Research and Experiment -- Urban Strategies Project Working Papers, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Paris Office -- Paris Conference Background Papers, Role of National Affairs Office Overseas (1 of 2), 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Paris Office -- Paris Conference Information, Observations of Paris (2 of 2), 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Patman, Wright -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background on Federal Law on Tax-Exempt Foundations, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Police Foundation -- Report on NYPD Consolidation, Response to Ford Foundation Trustees (1 of 3), 1970-1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Police Foundation -- Ford Foundation Grant Support, Report on Police in Amsterdam (2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Police Foundation -- Grantee Evaluation, Board of Directors (3 of 3), 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - President's Advisory Council on Minority Business Enterprise -- Background Papers (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - President's Advisory Council on Minority Business Enterprise -- Minutes, Status Updates on Council Activities (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Program Related Investments -- Ford Foundation Program Review and Budget Statement (1 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Program Related Investments -- Ford Foundation Review of PRIs and PRI Consultants (2 of 2), 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Public Agenda Foundation -- Proposal, Grant Review and Related Memoranda, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Public Interest Law -- Information Paper, Grants Involving Litigation, Background (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Public Interest Law -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Grants, Report on Public Interest Law Conference (2 of 2), 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pugh, Douglas -- Memoranda, Report on Minority Contractors Bonding Program, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - PUSH for Excellence, Inc. -- Correspondence with Jesse Jackson, Proposal, Site Visit, Grant and Grantee Reviews, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Quality of Work Center and Quality of Working Life -- Memoranda, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Quevedo, Edward T. (Director of Human Resources Institute, Claremont Colleges) -- Correspondence Re: Questions about Grant, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - R-General -- Racial Policy Issues Meeting, Royalty Income from Ford Foundation Publications, etc. (1 of 2), 1971-1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - R-General -- Aspen Institute Projects, Rural America Task Force, etc. (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Discussion: Basic Research Needs in Race and Ethnicity" (report by Shirley Teper), 1974 January 25 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Proposal, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- Meeting Agenda and Background, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Past and Present Foundation Funded Research on Race and Ethnicity", 1973 August (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- Preliminary Paper to Race and Ethnicity Staff Study, 1972 October 25 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Race and Ethnicity Task Force Memorandum and First Set of Background Papers", 1972 December 4 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Race and Ethnicity Task Force Readings", 1973 June (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Research on Race and Ethnicity: Reports on Federal (and some other) Agencies" (1 of 2), 1973 August (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Research on Race and Ethnicity: Reports on Federal (and some other) Agencies" (2 of 2), 1973 August (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Race and Ethnicity Task Force -- "Studies in Racial, Cultural, and Political Pluralism" (information paper), Memoranda, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - RAND Corporation/Institute -- Memoranda, Correspondence Re: Studies of New York City Government, Proposition 13, etc., 1968-1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Resources and Environment -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers on Ford Foundation Program, 1972-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Retirement and Thrift Plan -- Ford Foundation Personnel Handbooks, Memoranda, Reports (1 of 2), 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Retirement and Thrift Plan -- Ford Foundation Personnel Handbooks, Memoranda, Reports (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Rubinger, Michael -- Memoranda, Paper on Local Foundations, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - S-General -- The Child in Development Planning, U.S. Policy Towards Southern Africa, etc. (1 of 2), 1973-1977 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - S-General -- Donna E. Shalala, Sloan Commission on Government and Higher Education, etc. (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (1 of 4), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (2 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (3 of 4), 1973-1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Schrank, Robert -- Memoranda, Papers, Field Reports, Program and Proposal Evaluations of Labor Projects etc. (4 of 4), 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Seessel, Thomas V. -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers, Reports, Evaluations, 1971-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Self-Dealing by Certain Grantees, Report of an Inquiry into Possibility of, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Silberman, Charles E. -- Criminal Violence, Criminal Justice (book) -- Correspondence, Comments, Clippings, 1971-1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Theodore M. -- Memoranda Re: Internal Policy on Closing Out Backlog of Inactive Grants and Information on Individual Awards, 1975 June-July (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Social Development, Office of -- Memoranda Re: Budget and Staff Policy, Staff Meeting Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - South Bronx -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Board of Trustees Site Visit, Grant DAP Action (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - South Bronx -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Board of Trustees Site Visit, Grant DAP Action (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Southern Regional Council -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Reports on Employment in Rural South, etc., 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Southern Rural Development -- Summary of Task Force Report, Correspondence, 1977 January (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Stephenson, Edwin P. -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Work as Consultant, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Stern Family Fund, David R. Hunter -- Correspondence, Papers on Urban Poverty, Racial Inequality etc., 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Sturz, Herbert -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Minorities in Construction Industry, Redevelopment of Times Square, etc., 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sugarman, Jule M. -- Correspondence, Testimony, Proposal for a Decennial-Sabbatical Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Supported Work -- Correspondence, Reports, Papers (1 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Supported Work -- Correspondence, Reports, Papers (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Supported Work -- Ford Foundation Advisory Group on Supported Work Meeting, Washington, DC, 1974 April 4-5 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Supported Work Programs -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sviridoff, Mitchell -- Papers, Speeches on Urban Policy etc., 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Swedish Workers -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Report, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - T-General -- Kitty Teltsch Interview Questions etc., 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Taconic Foundation -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Youth Energy Corps, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Teenage Pregnancy -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers, Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Transitional Employment Enterprises, Inc. -- Memoranda, Correspondence Re: Supported Work, etc., 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - U-General -- Urban Environment Foundation, etc., 1972-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - United States Conference of Mayors -- Correspondence, Clippings, Proposal for Labor Management Relations Center, 1969-1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers National Service Center -- Correspondence Re: Criticism and Support for Awarding of Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Urban America, Inc. -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Minutes, Papers on New Towns, Affordable Housing etc., 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Urban Institute -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Evaluation of Institute, Speech on Inflation and Unemployment, 1973-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - V-General -- Voter Education Project, etc., 1968-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Vera Institute of Justice -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Reports, Background (1 of 2), 1965-1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Vera Institute of Justice -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Reports, Background (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - W-General -- Thomas J. Wattley, Jr., Wildcat Service Corporation, etc., 1974-1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Watts Labor Community Action Committee, Ted Watkins -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Evaluations of Shop Rite Markets (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Watts Labor Community Action Committee, Ted Watkins -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Evaluations of Shop Rite Markets (2 of 2), 1972-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Welfare -- Reports and Research on Welfare in New York City (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Welfare -- Reports and Research on Welfare in New York City (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Policy Meeting -- Memoranda, Background for Meeting, 1976 July 27 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- "Attitudes Toward Public Welfare Programs and Recipients" (survey by Natalie Jaffe), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Proposals, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- Papers, Clippings, Correspondence Re: Papers (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- Papers, Clippings, Correspondence Re: Papers (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- Project Description, DAP Proposal, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Policy Project -- Summaries of Welfare Policy Papers, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Reform -- Correspondence, Concept Paper on Job Creation and Equity Programs, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - White House Conference "To Fulfill These Rights" -- Conference Report, Speeches, Working Paper on National Action Programs, 1966 June 1-2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Whiting, Basil J. -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers, Reports on Occupational Safety, Public Policy and Social Organization Duties, etc., 1971-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Winnick, Louis -- Memoranda, Papers, Reports on American Governance, Visit to Sri Lanka, etc., 1968-1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Women -- "Attitude Survey Concerning the Role of Women at the Ford Foundation", 1970 December (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Women -- "The Changing Role of Women in U.S. Society" (report by Siobhan Oppenheimer-Nicolau), 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Women -- "Long Overdue: Full Partnership for Women in American Society" (report by Esther Peterson), Bio, Transcript of Presentation at Ford, 1971 October (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Women -- Memoranda, Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Women -- Memoranda and Proposals Re: Feminist Law Firms, 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Women -- "Recommendations for Women's Programs" [in Division of National Affairs], 1971 October (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Women -- "Survey of Foundation and Government Grants for Women's Rights and Opportunities, 1971-1975", 1975 November (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Women -- Task Force on Women -- Memoranda, Papers, Articles (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Women -- Task Force on Women -- Memoranda, Papers, Articles (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Women -- Task Force on Women -- Memoranda, Papers, Articles (3 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Women -- "The Women's Movement and Foundations" (transcript of meeting at Carnegie Building, NY, NY), 1971 September 17 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Women -- Women's Programs and Women at Ford Foundation -- Memoranda, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Women's Programs -- Memoranda, Meeting Agenda, Papers, Reports (1 of 5), 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Women's Programs -- Memoranda, Meeting Agenda, Papers, Reports (2 of 5), 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Women's Programs -- Memoranda, Meeting Agenda, Papers, Reports (3 of 5), 1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Women's Programs -- Memoranda, Meeting Agenda, Papers, Reports (4 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Women's Programs -- Memoranda, Meeting Agenda, Papers, Reports (5 of 5), 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Work in America Institute -- Correspondence, Meeting Summaries, Report on Job Strategies for Urban Youth, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Yankelovich, Daniel -- Public Agenda Foundation -- Memoranda, Papers on Attitudes Toward Economic Policy etc., 1977-1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Yerres, France -- Association for Cultural Development Conference on Industrial Housing, Symposium on Integrated Facilities for Community Educational and Cultural Activities, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Young, Milton -- Correspondence, Proposal to Continue Designing a New System of Educational Experiences for a Total Community (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Young, Milton -- Correspondence, Proposal to Continue Designing a New System of Educational Experiences for a Total Community (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Youth Employment -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Papers, Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Youth Employment and Demonstration Project, Graham Finney -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Proposals, Field Reports (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Youth Employment and Demonstration Project, Graham Finney -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Proposals, Field Reports (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Youth Unemployment -- Correspondence Re: Projects, Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Youth Unemployment Problems Meeting at Ford Foundation -- Minutes, Invitation List, 1977 November 16 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Z-General -- Zion Investment Associates, John E. Zuccotti, etc., 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Urban Affairs Institute -- Memoranda and Correspondence on Allegations of Mismanagement of Funds (1 of 2), 1968-1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Urban Affairs Institute -- Memoranda and Correspondence on Allegations of Mismanagement of Funds (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - The Woodlawn Organization (TWO), Finney Leon -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Clippings Re: Investigative Audit of Financial Management, 1972-1979 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Chronological Correspondence Files, 1975-1978; II; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box